Finding Aid for Elk Presbyterian Church (Peck, Mich.) records, 1888-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Elk Presbyterian Church (Peck, Mich.) records 1888-1972
Elk Presbyterian Church (Peck, Mich.).
0.5 linear feet
86876 Ba 2
Peck, Michigan, Presbyterian Church; minutes of congregation, trustees, and sessions.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records came from the Lake Huron Presbytery of the United Presbyterian Church (donor no. 4650 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
Elk Presbyterian Church in Peck, Michigan was organized September 2, 1888. The church dissolved December 31, 1972.
The record group contains session minutes, minutes of trustees, and community center records.
Subjects:
Peck (Mich.); United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.--Michigan--Peck.; Sanilac County (Mich.)
- Church records
  - Session records, 1888-1919; includes minutes, lists of members and other vital records (Box 1)
  - Minutes of congregational meetings, 1889-1908; includes financial records to 1921 (Box 1)
  - Community Center records, April 7, 1918-1938; includes minutes, financial records and vital records (Box 1)
  - Minutes of Trustee meetings and Congregational meeting held by the trustees, 1896-1916 (Box 1)
  - Session records,1913-1952; includes minutes, membership lists, baptisms (Box 1)
  - Session records, 1952-1973; includes membership lists and vital records (Box 1)
  - Guest book, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Historical materials (Box 1)
  - Legal and financial papers (Box 1)